S.S. Coronia
Marist Archives and Special Collections
S.S. Coronia
2.1.1.1.27
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1245
- S.S. Coronia, 2.1.1.1.27
  - Looking forward from lower deck, 1912 June 4; 6; 22059; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Crow’s nest, 1912 Just 6; 7; 22044; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Purser office and staff, 1912 June 7; 8; 22050; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Wireless operator and machinery, 1912 June 7; 9; 22054; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Promenade deck, 1912 June 8; 10; 22045; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Looking at aft from prow y boat, 1912 June 8; 11; 22046; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Upper deck and life boats, 1912 June 8; 12; 22049; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Looking aft from bridge, 1912 June 16; 13; 22060; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Shuffle board, 1912; 14; 4x5 (Box 1245)
  - Frank R. Roberson on upper deck, 1912; 15; 22061; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Air funnels and tusitanie[?], 1912; 16; 22071; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Bridge of tusetanie[?], 1912; 17; 22068; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Mr. Cubbin, purser, at Genoa Italy, 1912; 18; 22036; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Top deck, Frank R. Roberson on smoke stack, 1912 June 5; 19; 22051; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Automative engine director, 1912 June 5; 20; 22058; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Captain Barr by wheelhouse, 1912 June 6; 21; 22056; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Chief officer, 1912 June 8; 22; 22055; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Mr. Lister, 1912 June 9; 23; 22040; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Mr. Murus and Mr. Lister, 1912 June 9; 24; 22041; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Chief Officer Gronow, 1912; 25; 22066; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Chief Officer Gronow, 1912; 26; 22069; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Captain Barr, 1912; 27; 22070; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Ship at Naples, 1912; 28; 22020; 4x5 (Box 1245)
  - Fishguard Harbor, Wales, 1912 June 8; 29; 22052; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Fishguard Harbor, Wales, 1912 June 8; 30; 22053; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Coronia at Princess Street Landing and public buildings of Liverpool England, 1912 June 9; 31; 22047; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Public buildings in Liverpool, England, 1912 June 9; 32; 22048; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Public buildings in Liverpool, England from deck, 1912 June 9; 33; 22057; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - The crowd at pier in Liverpool, England, ship docking, 1912; 34; 22067; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Ship in Hus Kisson dock, Liverpool, England, 1912 June 11; 35; 22072; 31; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Rigby docks and flour mills, Liverpool England, 1912 June 11; 36; 22073; 32; 5x7 (Box 1245)
  - Funchal woman and child, 1912; 37; 23000; 1288; 4x5 (Box 1245)
  - Funchal men carrying hammock, 1912; 38; 23003; 4x5 (Box 1245)
  - Serving tea on deck, 1912; 39; 4x5 (Box 1245)
  - Island, taken from ship, 1912; 40; 4x5 (Box 1245)
  - City and water in distance, through trees, 1912; 41; 4x5 (Box 1245)